ANDREA MEI T. MAALA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

EAHXMEI.VERCEL.APP



CONTACT



eahxmaala@gmail.com



EDUCATION

Mapúa Malayan Colleges Laguna 2020-2024 B.S. in Computer Science

AWARDS & CERTIFICATIONS

• Deans Lister A.Y. 2020-2023

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS/SCSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript/jQuery
- TypeScript
- PHP
- ReactJS
- NextJS
- GSAP
- Figma

ABOUT

I am a detail-oriented, flexible, and dedicated worker who developed web applications utilizing user-friendly visuals and features. I also have volunteer experience as the Creatives Volunteer for Mapúa Malayan Colleges Laguna College of Computer Science Student Council, Creatives Director for Mapúa Malayan Colleges Laguna Supreme Student Council, and Art Director for Mapúa MCL Cup 2024, which shaped my ability to incorporate creativity to solve technical problems, deliver outputs in a fast-paced environment, and collaborate with diverse people.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT INTERN **Prosperna**

April 2024 - July 2024

- Developed a feature (Product Image Labels) for the merchant web platform.
- Conducted support tasks that involves User Interface (UI) enhancements in the merchant web platform.
- Developed custom and dynamic websites for potential clients using the Prosperna Page Builder.

WEB DEVELOPER AND USER-INTERFACE DESIGNER

e-ganapp - A Seamless Event Management System for Mapúa MCL (Thesis Project) September 2023 - August 2024

- Consulted with Mapúa MCL student organization heads and the Center for Student Activities and Discipline (CSAD) head to identify user needs regarding event management.
- Designed the web application interface for organizers, attendees, and admins.
- Developed the front-end for the organizer and attendee web platform.
- Aided event attendees in using the app during the "Technopreneurship: A
 Journey in Building Your Own Tech Startup" Seminar 2024 held in Mapúa MCL.

ART DIRECTOR

Mapúa Malayan Colleges Laguna Cup 2024 (Mapúa MCL Cup 2024) February 2024 - June 2024

- Collaborated with the Office for Corporate Communications (OCC) and Creatives
 Director to discuss design approaches and ensure branding consistency for the
- Designed merchandise and awarding materials appropriate to the requirements for Mapúa MCL Cup 2024.
- Managed associates to ensure that outputs are of quality and followed the event branding.

CREATIVES DIRECTOR

Mapúa Malayan Colleges Laguna Supreme Student Council (MMCL-SSC) May 2024 - July 2024

- Collaborated with the Creatives Committee and the Office for Corporate Communications (OCC) to discuss design approaches and ensure branding consistency for school events.
- Designed publication materials appropriate to the requirements of each events and announcement.
- Coordinated with other committees for sudden announcements and additional information related to publication material contents.
- Managed associates to ensure that outputs are of quality and maintained the branding consistency.

ANDREA MEI T. MAALA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

EAHXMEI.VERCEL.APP



CONTACT





eahxmaala@gmail.com



Blk 2 Lot 12 Phase 2 Ciudad De San Jose, Balibago, Sta Rosa, Laguna, Philippines 4026

EDUCATION

Mapúa Malayan Colleges Laguna

2020-2024

B.S. in Computer Science

AWARDS & CERTIFICATIONS

• Deans Lister A.Y. 2020-2023

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS/SCSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript/jQuery
- TypeScript
- PHP
- ReactJS
- NextJS
- GSAP
- Figma

EXPERIENCE

CREATIVES MANAGER

Mapúa Malayan Colleges Laguna Supreme Student Council (MMCL-SSC) August 2023 - May 2024

- Collaborated with the Creatives Committee and the Office for Corporate Communications (OCC) to discuss design approaches and ensure branding consistency for school events.
- Designed publication materials appropriate to the requirements of each events and announcement.
- Designed custom assets such as illustrations and logos for publication materials.
- · Coordinated with other committees for sudden announcements and additional information related to publication material contents.
- Assisted the Creatives Director to further ensure a positive and efficient environment in the committee.

CREATIVES ASSOCIATE

Mapúa Malayan Colleges Laguna Supreme Student Council (MMCL-SSC)

August 2021 - August 2023

- · Collaborated with the Creatives Committee and the Office for Corporate Communications (OCC) to discuss design approaches and ensure branding consistency for school events.
- Designed publication and awarding materials appropriate to the requirements of each events.
- Designed custom assets such as illustrations and logos for publication materials.

CREATIVES VOLUNTEER

Mapúa Malayan Colleges Laguna College of Computer Science Student Council (MMCL-CCIS SC)

April 2021 - June 2024

- · Collaborated with the CCIS Student Council and the CCIS Dean to discuss design approaches and ensure branding consistency for CCIS events.
- Designed publication materials, merchandise, and awarding materials appropriate to the requirements of each events.